As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's a lodge mystery!
!قضيّة اليوم غموض منزل جبلي
Who's the mysterious bandaged man?
من هو رجل الضماد الغامض؟
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
Huh? That's strange...
...ماذا؟ غريب
The lodge should be right around here...
...يُفترض أن يكون السّكن في هذه الأرجاء
Say, we're not lost, are we?
أيمكن أنّنا ضللنا طريقنا؟
Eep...
!بـ... بالطبع لا
We're just taking a little side trip!
نسلك طريقاً التفافيّاً فحسب
We're lost.
ضللنا
Oh? Someone's walking...
...ماذا؟ أحدهم يمشي
I wonder if he's going to the lodge too?
أتساءل لو سيذهب للمنزل أيضاً؟
I don't think so...
...لا-لا أظنّ
You're late, Ran! What were you doing?!
تأخّرتِ يا ران! ماذا كنتِ تفعلين؟
Sorry, Sonoko!
!آسفة يا سونوكو
I'm nice enough to let you stay at my family's lodge
كنتُ لطيفة بما يكفي لدعوتكِ لمنزل عائلتي الجبليّ وتصلين متأخّرة
I figured you'd bring him.
جلبته معك بالفعل
You should be more considerate, Conan-kun!
أظهر بعض المراعاة يا كونان-كن
As if you're one to talk...
كأنّك أهلٌ لقول ذلك
Keep hanging around this twerp and you'll never fall in love!
بوجود هذا الصغير حولنا لن نقع في الحُب أبداً
Love?
الحُب؟
Yeah! We're here to meet some wonderful guys!
أجل، نحن هنا للقاء شبّان رائعين ،وبالطبيعة تحيطنا
And with nature all around us,
!سنعيش تجارب عاطفية كالأحلام معهم
Oh yeah, I forgot she's that kind of person...
...صحيح، إنّها من هذا الصنف
Oh? These "wonderful guys" aren't here yet?
ماذا؟ لم يأت "الشبّان الرائعون" بعد؟
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تقولينه؟
My sister's friends got here long ago
وصل أصدقاء أختي منذ فترة وهم يستريحون في غرفهم الآن
That reminds me, is one of their faces wrapped in bandages?
تذكّرت، أبينهم شخصٌ وجهه ملفوف بالضماد؟
Bandages? No...
ضماد؟ كلا، لا أحد من القادمين مُصاب
But we just saw--
...لكنّنا رأينا قبل قليل
Maybe he lives nearby, then...
...ربما يعيش بالقرب إذاً
Alright, stop being a weirdo and put your stuff away!
دعيك من الكلام الغريب وأفرغي أمتعتك
You guys' room is upstairs!
غرفتكما في الأعلى
Okay!
!حسناً
Wait, look at all these rooms up here...
لحظة، توجد غرف كثيرة هنا
Which one is ours?
أيّ واحدة... هي غرفتنا؟
I'm sorry! My mistake!
!آ-آسفة! أخطأت
Here we go! This is ours, Conan-kun!
!ها هي! يبدو أنّ هذه غرفتنا يا كونان-كن
Geez, learn to knock before opening doors!
يا إلهي، تعلّمي قرع الباب قبل الفتح
You're all from the same circle?
كلّكم من نفس المجموعة إذاً؟
Yeah! They all made films together during my sister's college days.
أجل، جميعهم صوّروا أفلام معاً أثناء دراسة أختي في الجامعة
The five closest people got together for the first time in two years!
اجتمع الأشخاص الخمسة المقرّبون لأوّل مرّة منذ عامين
Next to Ran is Ota-san,
حسناً... من بجانب ران هو أوتا-سان الذي كان يلعب دور البطل عادةً
who usually played the leading role!
(أوتا ماسارو (24 سمسار سيّارات أجنبية
Yo!
مرحباً
Next to him is Sumiya-san, our cameraman!
وبجواره سوميا-سان الذي كان المصوّر
Hiya!
كيف الحال؟
Our stage manager, Takahashi-san!
ومدير المسرح تاكاهاشي-سان
Hello!
مـ-مرحباً
I apologize for earlier!
أعتذر عمَّ فعلت قبل قليل
That's okay!
لا مشكلة
Huh? What did you do?
ماذا؟ ما الذي فعلته؟
Next up is our makeup and wardrobe person,
حسنٌ، التالية هي مسؤولة المكياج والثياب
my sister, who is also looking for a husband!
والتي تبحث عن زوجٍ حالياً، أختي الكبرى
That's enough.
يكفي هذا
And last is our director, scriptwriter, and club president--
والأخيرة هي المخرجة وكاتبة النصّ ورئيسة النادي
Ikeda Chikako-san!
إيكيدا تشيكاكو-سان
Nice to meet you.
سُررت بلقائك
The same Ikeda Chikako-san who wrote the very latest movie, "Blue Kingdom"?!
إيكيدا تشيكاكو-سان نفسها التي كتبت فيلم "المملكة الزرقاء" الأخير؟
That's right!
صحيح
She wrote it during college and it started her career, right?
كتبته أثناء دراستها، وكان عملها الرسميّ الأوّل، صحيح؟
Don't drag up old stories like that!
توقفي عن قصّ حكايا الماضي
I hear there's talk about your next movie...
هناك شائعات عن فيلمٍ قادم لك
Ikeda-sensei! How about a word for your fans?
إذاً يا إيكيدا سينسي، ألديكِ كلمة لمعجبيك؟
Stop being silly, Sumiya-kun.
توقّف عن التصرف بسخافة يا سوميا-كن
You still love to tape things, I see...
لا تزال الكاميرا ملتصقةً بيدك
Yeah! I can't kick the habit!
أجل، لا يمكنني التوقف عن التصوير
Hey, Takahashi! Have you gotten fatter?
بالمناسبة يا تاكاهاشي، هل أصحبت أبدن؟
Yeah, I guess I'm about 100 kilograms now...
ماذا؟ لعلّي أزن 100 كيلو الآن
I can't get you in frame anymore!
لا تتسع في إطار الكاميرا حتّى
This certainly brings back memories of college!
وجودي معكم يعيد لي ذكريات الجامعة حقاً
And Atsuko...
...وذكريات أتسوكو
I'm sure she'd be here now if she hadn't done that...
...كانت لتكون هنا حتماً لو لم يحصل ذلك
Atsuko?
أتسوكو؟
Let's not talk about her!
!لنمتنع عن ذكرها
Chikako...
...تشيكاكو
I took time out of my busy schedule to be here.
اقتطعتُ وقتاً من أشغالي للقدوم هنا
Let's not talk about someone who died two years ago!
لا تتكلّمي عن شخص مات قبل عامين
I'm sorry...
آسفة
Celebrities sure do say strange things...
المشاهير يتكلمون بأسلوبٍ مختلف حقاً
What's that mean?!
!ما قصدك؟
Now, now, you two!
!رويدكما
I'll go make dinner now, so just make yourselves at home!
سأعدّ العشاء فوراً، لذا اعتبروا أنفسكم في منازلكم
In that case, I'll go finish fixing the roof!
سأذهب لإنهاء إصلاح السقف إذاً
They said it was going to rain this evening!
فيُقال أنّها ستُمطر هذا المساء
I'd appreciate that, Takahashi-kun!
أجل، أنا ممتنة لك يا تاكاهاشي-كن، توخّ الحذر
Yeah!
أجل
Sounds like the perfect kind of work for a set designer!
هذا عملٌ يليق بمصمم المسرح حقّاً
What do you say the rest of us play cards?
ما رأيك أن نلعب نحن الباقون بطاقات؟
Yeah! I'll play!
!أجل! سألعب
Where're you going, Chikako?!
أين تذهبين يا تشيكاكو؟
For a walk.
للتنزه
Wait!
!انتظري يا تشيكاكو
Takahashi said it's gonna rain!
قال تاكاهاشي أنّها ستُمطر
Come on, Chikako!
!أنت، تشيكاكو
It's really coming down...
إنّه يهطل بغزارة
There's no enjoying the view now.
لن نستطيع الاستمتاع بالمنظر الآن
Hey, Ran!
ران
Isn't he dreamy?
ألا تجدينه مناسباً؟
He's like so cool and suave-- totally my type!
!يبدو رائعاً وواثقاً، إنّه صنفي تماماً
You think?
حقاً؟
Oh, that's right, you have Shinichi-kun!
نسيت، لديك شينتشي-كن، صحيح؟
It's too bad he couldn't come with you...
من المؤسف أنّه لم يأت معك
As if! I'd bust him upside the head if he were here!
!من يهتمّ له؟ كنت سأبرحه ضرباً لو كان هنا
He is here.
لكنّه هنا
Say. Would you like to take a walk with me?
أخبريني، ما رأيك أن ترافقيني في نزهة؟
I'd love to!
فلا شيء لديك لتفعليه
After all, you're not doing anything.
لكن المطر يهطل خارجاً
But it's raining outside...
المشي في المطر يبعث الحيوية
Walks in the rain can be invigorating.
!هيّا بنا
Wait!
!ا-انتظر
That bastard!
!ذ-ذاك الوغد
She'll pay!
!لن أسامحك
That lousy Ran! She has Shinichi-kun!
!ران تلك لديها شينتشي-كن
Yeah!
!صحيح
Maybe I'll steal Shinichi-kun from her!
!ربما سأسرق شينتشي-كن منها
No. No, you won't.
كلا، لن تفعلي
Eh? There's someone you like?
حقاً؟ لديكِ شخص يعجبك؟
Yes...
أجل
But you don't know when he'll be back, right?
لكن لا تعرفين متى قد يعود، صحيح؟
You should dump the cold-hearted jerk
عليكِ هجر بارد الإحساس ذاك
and find a better man!
والعثور على شابٍ جديد
How about I teach you...
...ما رأيك بأن أعلّمك
...what adult love is?
كيف هو حُبّ البالغين؟
Wait--
...انتظـ
Lightning!
!رعد
Hey!
!انتظري
Whoa, that was a really close one!
أخافني ذلك، كانت الصاعقة قريبة
Oh no! They're gone!
!تبّاً! اختفيا
Ahh! Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Really, now...
يا إلهي
I think I might be lost...
...ربما ضللت الطريق
Ota-san, where are you?
أين أنت يا أوتا-سان؟
Say something if you're there! Ota-san!
!أجبني إن كنت موجوداً! أوتا-سان
Ran!
!ران
That's--
...إنّه
What are you screaming about--
...ما الخطب يا ران
Damn it!
!تبّاً
Who was that?!
!من كان ذاك الشخص؟
A man in bandages?!
رجل بضماد؟
Yeah! He attacked Ran in the forest!
!أجل! هاجم ران في الغابة
You serious?!
حقّاً؟
Oh? You guys didn't see him?
ماذا؟ لم يره أحدكم؟
Weren't the three of you in the forest too?
ألم تكونوا الثلاثة في الغابة؟
I just went looking for Ran-chan--
لم أره، ذهبت للبحث عن ران-تشان بعدما انفصلت عنّي
I didn't see anything like that...
ولم يكن هناك شيء كذاك
We didn't see him either, right, Chikako?
لم نره نحن أيضاً، صحيح يا تشيكاكو؟
We?
نحن؟ اختفيتَ وحدك
I went to get an umbrella!
!كنتُ قد ذهبت لجلب مظلّة
Are you sure you weren't afraid of the lightning?
لم يخفك الرعد ورجعت هارباً؟
Chikako!
!تشيكاكو
What?!
!ماذا؟
Now, now, you two!
!رويدكما
I guess it's almost over between them...
...ربما اقتربت نهايتهما
Hey, did you see the guy?
لم تري الرجل يا أختي؟
He ran toward the lodge...
ركض نحو المنزل
No, I didn't see anything...
كلا، لم أرَ أحداً
Did you see him, Takahashi-kun?
هل رأيته يا تاكاهاشي-كن؟
I was on the roof the entire time,
كنتُ فوق السقف طوال الوقت
but I don't remember seeing anyone like that...
ولا أتذكر رؤية شخصٍ كذاك
But I did see someone strange by the bridge
لكنّي رأيت شخصاً غريباً قرب الجسر
I couldn't really see his face,
لم أرَ وجهه بوضوح
but he was wearing a black cape and a hood.
لكن كان يرتدي معطفاً أسود وقلنسوة
Yes! That's the person who attacked me!
!أجل! ذاك هو الرجل الذي هاجمني
Right, Conan-kun?
صحيح يا كونان-كن؟
Yeah!
أجل
I saw the same guy when I got here!
رأيتُ ذاك الشخص عندما وصلت أيضاً
Same here! But I figured he lived nearby...
وأنا، لكنّني ظننته يعيش في الجوار
That can't be!
!هذا مستحيل
There are only two or three lodges on the other side of the bridge,
فلا يوجد سوى منزلين أو ثلاث على الجانب الآخر البعيد من الجسر
and there's a mountain on this side...
وهنا جبل يحجز الطريق
Then who was that guy?!
!من كان ذاك الرجل إذاً؟
We should call the police!
!لنتّصل بالشرطة بأيّ حال
Yes!
!أ-أجل
What? The phone's not working?!
!ماذا؟ لا يعمل الهاتف؟
But it was working this afternoon...
أجل، مع أنّه كان يعمل ظهيرة اليوم
Maybe the phones are down because of that lightning strike?
ربما قطعت الصاعقة الأخيرة خطوط الهاتف
It was him! That bandaged man cut the line!
!كان هو! رجل الضماد ذاك هو من قطع الخطّ
It was him!
!كان هو! كان هو
Hey, Takahashi!
!تاكاهاشي
Wait!
!انتظر
What is it?!
!ما الأمر؟ ماذا هناك؟
The bridge is out!
!سقط الجسر
What happened?!
ماذا حصل؟
The bridge is out.
سقط الجسر
Probably fell on its own. It was pretty old.
ربما سقط من تلقاء نفسه، فقد كان قديماً
No.
كلا
Someone cut it down.
قطعه أحدهم
Take a look at this bridge support.
انظر لعمادة الجسر هذه
What the hell?! It's been chopped up!
!ما هذا؟! تملأها آثار القطع
Somebody used some sort of blade...
...فهمت، استعمل أحدهم شفرةً
But who on earth would do this?
لكن من فعل ذلك؟
It was that guy! He did this too!
!إنّه هو! هذا من فعله أيضاً
Oh, come on!
!يكفي هذا
This "bandaged man" is ridiculous!
ما هراء رجل الضماد هذا؟
He attacked the girl in the forest, cut the phone line,
هاجم فتاةً في الغابة وقطع خطّ الهاتف وأسقط الجسر كي يستمتع برؤية الخوف على وجوهنا
If we keep getting afraid,
إن تركنا الخوف يتسلّل لنا أكثر سنعطيه ما يريد تماماً
Chikako...
...تشيكاكو
Anyway, it's dark out, so our only choice
بأيّ حال، خيّم الظلام الآن
is to wait until tomorrow morning.
فلا أمامنا سوى الانتظار للصباح للمغادرة
Plus this "bandaged man" everyone's worked up about
كما أنّ رجل الضماد الذي يشغلكم هذا لا يزال مُختبئاً في الغابة غالباً
Yes...
أجل
Oh?
ماذا؟
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
I'm going to bed now. I'm suddenly tired.
سأخلد للنوم الآن، فأشعر بالإرهاق فجأةً، لا أحتاج عشاءً
Chikako...
...تشيكاكو
Sorry for making you help, Ran-chan!
أعتذر على جعلك تساعدينني يا ران-تشان
No problem! I always do this at home!
لا مشكلة، أقوم بهذا في منزلنا دوماً
What a reunion this has turned into...
انقلب حال لمّ الشمل هذا تماماً
Everyone's suddenly unsociable...
أصبح الجميع متضايقين
It's all because you mentioned that incident!
هذا لأنّك ذكرتِ أمرها
You mean about Atsuko-san?
تقصدين أتسوكو-سان؟
The girl that had something happen two years ago--
الفتاة التي حصل لها شيءٌ ما قبل عامين
That's enough, Conan-kun!
!يكفي يا كونان-كن
She killed herself. Two years ago.
انتحرت أتسوكو، قبل عامين
She was a member of our filmmaking group, too!
كانت من فريق إنتاج الأفلام أيضاً
Then she suddenly hanged herself in her room,
لكنّها شنقت نفسها فجأةً في غرفتها
and everyone stopped meeting after that.
وتوقّف الجميع عن الاجتماع بعدها
We were all so close, too...
مع أنّنا كنّا مقرّبين جداً
That's why I asked everyone here for a long-overdue reunion!
لذا طلبتُ منهم القدوم هنا للمّ شمل بعد انقطاع طويل
So let's not talk about that anymore, alright?
لذا لنكفّ عن ذكر الموضوع، اتّفقنا يا كونان-كن؟
Alright.
أجل
Man, I'm starving.
أتضوّر جوعاً
Oh? Where's Chikako?
ماذا؟ أين تشيكاكو؟
She went to bed early.
قالت أنّها مرهقة وستنام
Takahashi-kun! Dinner's ready!
!تاكاهاشي-كن! العشاء جاهز
I'll be down in a sec.
سآتي قريباً
Well? Is the roof fixed?
كيف الأمر؟ هل أصلحت السقف؟
Yeah, for the most part.
أجل، تقريباً
Smile, you two!
!حسناً، ابتسما
Get down here, Takahashi!
!انزل بسرعة يا تاكاهاشي! سيبرد الطعام
Yeah, I'm coming.
حسناً، قادم الآن
Who're you?!
!مـ-من أنت؟
What is it?!
!ما الخطب؟
There's someone by the downstairs window!
!يوجد شخصٌ عند نافذة الطابق السفليّ
By the window?
عند النافذة؟
Chikako!
!تشيكاكو
Damn! It's too dark to see where they went!
!تبّاً! لا يمكننا رؤية أين ذهبا في الظلام
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Alright! Let's follow the kid!
!حسنٌ! لنتبع الصبيّ
Lock the doors and wait here!
!لتنتظر الفتيات هنا وتقفلن الأبواب
Come on, Takahashi!
!أسرع يا تاكاهاشي
Eh? Me, too?!
!ماذا؟ أنا أيضاً؟
Yes, you too!
!بالطبع
Wait for me!
!ا-انتظروني
It's a leg!
!إنّها ساق
Don't tell me it's Chikako's?!
!أ-أيمكن أنّها لتشيكاكو؟
There's an arm over here!
!توجد ذراع هنا
What the hell's goin' on?!
يا للهول
Let's split up and look!
!لننفصل ونبحث عنها
Chikako! Chikako!
!تشيكاكو! تشيكاكو
Chikako! Where are you?!
!أين أنت يا تشيكاكو؟
Chikako?
تشيكاكو؟
Chikako! Say something! Chikako!
!تشيكاكو! تماسكي! تشيكاكو
Yeah, she had been murdered...
...أجل، قُتلت
...by the time we got there.
مع وقت وصولنا
This can't be happening!
...لا-لا يمكن
For now, we covered the body with my jacket
غطّينا الجثة بمعطفي للوقت الراهن وتركناها في الغابة
Why would someone kill Chikako-san?!
لمَ قد يقتل أحدهم تشيكاكو-سان؟
It's all my fault!
!إنّها غلطتي
If only I hadn't planned this reunion,
...لو لم أخطط للقاء لمّ الشمل هذا
she'd still be--
...لما حصل
That's not true, Ayako! It's not your fault!
ليس صحيحاً يا أياكو، ليست غلطتك
That bandaged man is to blame!
!إنّها غلطة رجل الضماد ذاك
That crazed murderer who ran off with Chikako
ذاك القاتل الذي هرب بتشيكاكو
before our very eyes!
!أمام أنظارنا
What do we do if he comes back?
ماذا نفعل لو هاجمنا مُجدداً؟
We'll be fine if we lock the place down.
سنكون بخير طالما نقفل المكان
Chikako was careless enough to stroll around outside.
فقد أهملت تشيكاكو بتجوّلها خارجاً في هذا الوقت المتأخّر
Anyway, let's forget about this and get some shut-eye.
بأيّ حال، لننسَ الموضوع سريعاً ونخلد للنوم
Ota! How can you--
...أوتا، كيف لك
He's right. It's getting late.
صحيح، تأخّر الوقت
Let's make sure everything is locked and get some rest.
لنتحقق من إقفال كلّ شيء مُجدداً وننم
We'll climb down the mountain and get the police tomorrow.
سننزل من الجبل صباحاً ونخبر الشرطة
Yeah...
أجل
Front door's locked.
الباب الأمامي مُقفل
All that's left is our rooms...
تبقّت غرفنا فقط
What are you doing, Conan-kun?
ما الخطب يا كونان-كن؟
Chikako-san's slippers aren't here.
خُفّا تشيكاكو-سان ليسا هنا
Slippers?
خُفّاها؟
If she went out the front door, her slippers should be here.
،إذا خرجت تشيكاكو-سان من الباب الأمامي فيُفترض أنّ خُفيّها هنا
She might not have left from here.
ربما لم تغادر من هنا
What if the guy snuck into the lodge
ماذا لو تسلل ذاك الرجل للمنزل وهاجم تشيكاكو-سان النائمة في الطابق الثاني؟
Of course he didn't, Sonoko!
هذا مستحيل يا سونوكو
Remember? When Conan-kun and the others ran after him,
أتذكرين؟ عندما لاحق كونان-كن والبقية ذاك الرجل
you, me, and Ayako-san split up and checked all the locks!
انفصلتُ وأنت وأياكو-سان وتحققنا من كلّ الأقفال
Chikako-san's room wasn't in shambles,
لم تكن هناك فوضى في غرفة تشيكاكو-سان
and the window was locked from the inside.
والنافذة مغلقة من الداخل
But...
...لكن
I'm almost certain she went outside.
أنا متأكدٌ أنّها خرجت
After all, she was wearing shoes.
فقد كانت ترتدي حذاءً
Her leg had been chopped off, though.
رغم أنّ ساقها قد قُطعت
I see...
هكذا إذاً
Hey, does this lodge have any other exits?
أخبريني، أتوجد مخارج أخرى لهذا المنزل؟
Yeah. The back door.
أجل، الباب الخلفي
A back door?!
الباب الخلفي؟
This is the back door.
هذا الباب الخلفي
Here we go! These are definitely Chikako-san's slippers!
ها هما، خفّاها. إنّهما لتشيكاكو-سان بلا شك
We didn't leave any spare ones out!
فلم يكن لدينا أزواج إضافية
So that means Chikako-san went out this way...
خرجت تشيكاكو-سان من هنا إذاً
Yeah, probably.
أجل، على الأرجح
But why did she go out this way and not the front door?
لكن لمَ خرجت من هنا وليس الباب الأمامي؟
It's almost like she was trying to sneak out unseen...
كأنّها كانت تحاول التسلّل دون أن يراها أحد
Say, it's really muddy here--
المكان مُوحل، هنا أكان يستعمل أحدهم هذا الباب؟
Yeah, it was probably my sister;
لعلّها كانت أختي، فمفتاح الغاز وأشياء أخرى توجد في الفناء الخلفي
Well, we found her slippers, so let's go to bed now.
وجدنا خُفّاها، فلنخلد للنوم الآن
Alright!
أ-أجل
There! Now our room's okay too, Conan-kun!
!حسنٌ، غرفتنا بأمان الآن يا كونان-كن
Conan-kun?
كونان-كن؟
Stop worrying, everything'll be all right!
لا تقلق، سيكون كلّ شيءٍ بخير
If the bandaged man shows up again,
،إذا هاجمنا رجل الضماد مُجدداً !سأسحقه بالكاراتيه
Okay!
!حـ-حسناً
Yeah, right! When he attacked you in the forest you were too scared to do anything!
مليئة بالجرأة رغم أنّ الخوف جمّدك عندما هاجمك في الغابة
Say, why do you think he attacked you, anyway?
بالمناسبة، لمَ هاجمك بالتحديد؟
I don't know. Maybe it didn't matter who.
لا أدري، ربما لم تهم الضحيّة
Say, Ran-neechan.
أخبريني يا ران-نيتشان أهناك أحدٌ يكنّ ضغينةً لك؟
Like anyone whose face you injured with karate?
مثل شخص سحقتِ وجهه بالكاراتيه؟
Of course not!
!بالطبع لا
Now go to sleep!
!اخلد للنوم وحسب
Okay.
حاضر
But there's something odd about that bandaged man.
لكن هناك أمرٌ غريب حيال رجل الضماد ذاك
If he took Chikako-san, who left out the back door,
،لو أخذ تشيكاكو-سان التي خرجت من الباب الخلفي
then why would he go around to the front door for us to see?
فلمَ استدار وأظهر نفسه لنا عند الباب الأمامي؟
To make us afraid? Or perhaps--
...لإخافتنا؟ أم ربما
Hey.
أخبرني
Can I sleep with you?
أيمكنني النوم معك؟
Eh? What for?
لـ-لمَ؟
Just because.
لا يهم
Is it because you're afraid?
أيمكن أنّك خائفة؟
Sweet dreams, Conan-kun.
عمت مساءً يا كونان-كن
Girls have some nerve!
يا إلهي، يا للفتيات
Now where was I?
حسنٌ، أين كنت؟
That bandaged man had just--
...رجل الضماد كان قد
As I was saying...
...كما قلت
Oh no! I can't think!
!كلا! لا يمكنني التفكير
Well, this is a crazed murderer we're dealing with;
حسنٌ، نحن نتعامل مع قاتلٍ مجنون
this is a job for the police, not me...
هذا عمل الشرطة وليس عملي
Time for sleep...
...لأنم
Can I sleep?
لكن أيمكنني النوم؟
He's after Ran!
!إنّه يستهدف ران
Wake up, Ran!
!استيقظي يا ران
Ran! Ran!
!ران! ران
Damn it!
!تبّاً
Ow!
!هذا مؤلم
Oh no! I sprained my ankle!
!سحقاً! لويتُ كاحلي
Once Ran falls asleep, there's no waking her up!
!لا شيء يوقظ ران بعدما تغطّ في النوم
Isn't there anything around here?!
أليس هناك ما يمكنني استعماله؟
That's it! The Voice-Altering Bow Tie!
!وجدتُها! ربطة تغيير الصوت
I'll crank up the volume, and--
...سأرفع الصوت لأعلى حدّ و
Get up!
!استيقظي
Ran! Conan-kun! What's going on?!
!ران! كونان-كن! ما الذي يجري؟
Open the door! Conan-kun! Ran!
!افتحا الباب! كونان-كن! ران
Wait!
!انتظر
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Damn it! Why?!
!اللعنة! لمَ؟
Why is he after Ran?!
!لمَ يستهدف ران؟
The bandaged man is after Ran!
!رجل الضماد يلاحق ران فعلاً
But why her?!
لكن لمَ هي؟
Something's nagging at me...
...هناك ما حيّر بالي
Think back, Ran-neechan!
!تذكّري يا ران-نيتشان
I just figured it out...
...لقد اكتشفت
I know who killed Chikako-san!
!هويّة المجرم الذي قتل تشيكاكو-سان
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Mountain Lodge Bandage Man Murder Case (Part 2)."
جريمة قتل رجل ضماد المنزل الجبلي (الجزء الثاني)
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Piano wires.
أسلاك بيانو